[ {
  "num" : "1",
  "question" : "감지",
  "answer" : "덕지",
  "options" : [ "하장", "애애", "덕지", "불만" ]
}, {
  "num" : "2",
  "question" : "개과",
  "answer" : "천선",
  "options" : [ "상종", "다난", "첨화", "천선" ]
}, {
  "num" : "3",
  "question" : "과유",
  "answer" : "불급",
  "options" : [ "불급", "탈태", "익선", "천선" ]
}, {
  "num" : "4",
  "question" : "금상",
  "answer" : "첨화",
  "options" : [ "우지", "첨화", "다식", "마비" ]
}, {
  "num" : "5",
  "question" : "금지",
  "answer" : "옥엽",
  "options" : [ "팔구", "다식", "옥엽", "불망" ]
}, {
  "num" : "6",
  "question" : "다다",
  "answer" : "익선",
  "options" : [ "애락", "불망", "성시", "익선" ]
}, {
  "num" : "7",
  "question" : "다사",
  "answer" : "다난",
  "options" : [ "다난", "우지", "불급", "일관" ]
}, {
  "num" : "8",
  "question" : "동문",
  "answer" : "서답",
  "options" : [ "서답", "일관", "북답", "마비" ]
}, {
  "num" : "9",
  "question" : "만수",
  "answer" : "무강",
  "options" : [ "불급", "불망", "무강", "상종" ]
}, {
  "num" : "10",
  "question" : "막상",
  "answer" : "막하",
  "options" : [ "막하", "정리", "우지", "막중" ]
}, {
  "num" : "11",
  "question" : "문전",
  "answer" : "성시",
  "options" : [ "불급", "성시", "정리", "미인" ]
}, {
  "num" : "12",
  "question" : "박학",
  "answer" : "다식",
  "options" : [ "이조", "상종", "우지", "다식" ]
}, {
  "num" : "13",
  "question" : "불평",
  "answer" : "불만",
  "options" : [ "불만", "다식", "우지", "일관" ]
}, {
  "num" : "14",
  "question" : "새옹",
  "answer" : "지마",
  "options" : [ "불급", "성시", "지마", "정리" ]
}, {
  "num" : "15",
  "question" : "십중",
  "answer" : "팔구",
  "options" : [ "익선", "팔구", "정리", "상종" ]
}, {
  "num" : "16",
  "question" : "십시",
  "answer" : "일반",
  "options" : [ "애애", "일반", "천선", "불급" ]
}, {
  "num" : "17",
  "question" : "오매",
  "answer" : "불망",
  "options" : [ "불망", "지마", "이조", "정리" ]
}, {
  "num" : "18",
  "question" : "유유",
  "answer" : "상종",
  "options" : [ "다식", "상종", "미인", "일관" ]
}, {
  "num" : "19",
  "question" : "일석",
  "answer" : "이조",
  "options" : [ "삼조", "사조", "이조", "오조" ]
}, {
  "num" : "20",
  "question" : "일편",
  "answer" : "단심",
  "options" : [ "단심", "불만", "미인", "정리" ]
}, {
  "num" : "21",
  "question" : "적반",
  "answer" : "하장",
  "options" : [ "반지", "하장", "우지", "불급" ]
}, {
  "num" : "22",
  "question" : "좌지",
  "answer" : "우지",
  "options" : [ "지우", "불망", "우지", "익선" ]
}, {
  "num" : "23",
  "question" : "죽마",
  "answer" : "고우",
  "options" : [ "고우", "상종", "일편", "다식" ]
}, {
  "num" : "24",
  "question" : "천고",
  "answer" : "마비",
  "options" : [ "마비", "이조", "불급", "단심" ]
}, {
  "num" : "25",
  "question" : "초지",
  "answer" : "일관",
  "options" : [ "사지", "정리", "일관", "다난" ]
}, {
  "num" : "26",
  "question" : "팔방",
  "answer" : "미인",
  "options" : [ "미인", "지마", "불만", "사방" ]
}, {
  "num" : "27",
  "question" : "화기",
  "answer" : "애애",
  "options" : [ "에에", "불급", "애애", "천선" ]
}, {
  "num" : "28",
  "question" : "환골",
  "answer" : "탈태",
  "options" : [ "탈태", "미인", "탈퇴", "상종" ]
}, {
  "num" : "29",
  "question" : "희로",
  "answer" : "애락",
  "options" : [ "불만", "애락", "우지", "정리" ]
}, {
  "num" : "30",
  "question" : "회자",
  "answer" : "정리",
  "options" : [ "지리", "천선", "불망", "정리" ]
} ]